四个月前
知道什么叫雪盲症吗
Know what photokeratitis is?
光盲症呢
How about flash blindness?
其实一样
The same thing, really.
都是过度暴露在紫外线下引起的
Both caused by excessive exposure to ultraviolet light.
角膜灼伤
Cornea burns,
无法承受光的强度
unable to handle the light's intensity.
让你暂时失明
And you temporarily lose your vision.
理论上
The theory--
你只会有心理痛苦
pain is only psychological
因为视网膜上没有痛觉感受器
since the retina has no pain receptors.
这种特别的方式是911事件后
This particular model was built by Homeland Security
国安局用来折磨犯人的
to torture prisoners after 9/11.
不幸的是  后来被禁止了
Unfortunately, it was banned...
因为有些混蛋永远瞎了
after some of those fuckers went blind for good.
黑吃黑
第四季
第三集
他妈的放我出去
Let me the fuck out!
我他妈要杀了你
I'll fucking kill you!
混蛋  我他妈要杀了你
Motherfucker, I will fucking kill you!
二十个月前
谢谢
Thank you.
邦克
Hey, Bunker.
医生说你不会有事
Doctor says you're gonna be all right.
三个月前
没事  没事
It's okay. It's okay.
你安全了  看着我
You're safe. Look at me.
没事了
It's okay.
你发烧了
You have a fever.
你的身体在抵抗感染
Your body is fighting off the infection.
我要把你的头扶起来  好吗
I'm gonna lift up your head, okay?
咽下去  很好
Hold it down. That's good.
好了
Okay.
很好
That's good.
就是这样  咽下去
That's it, swallow.
我再给你清理一下伤口  好吗
I'm gonna clean you up a little bit more, okay?
会有点疼
It's gonna sting.
你知道...
Do you have any idea...
自己在做什么吗
what you're even doing?
你还活着  不是吗
You're still breathing, aren't you?
是你
You.
要邀请我们进去吗
You gonna invite us in?
虽然斯托上校是个疯子
Colonel Stowe may have been crazy,
但他仍然是军人  什么都记录得清清楚楚
but he was still military and kept meticulous records.
热那亚事件后  刑事调查局掌握了他的资料
After Genoa, CID seized his files.
我用想尽一切办法
I tried everything I could to get my hands on them,
但都没拿到
but I kept hitting brick walls.
所以她就去找你了吗
So then she came back to you?
你知道偷盗是我的专长
Y'all know busting through walls is my specialty.
所以你们从刑事调查局把热那亚的资料偷出来了吗
Okay, so then you stole the Genoa files from CID?
只要你有足够的说服力  根本不用偷
Don't need to steal when you got the power of persuasion.
虽然花的时间有点长
Took a little longer than I would have liked.
但最终还是找对了五角大楼的档案员
Finally got to the right record clerk in the Pentagon.
为了让我不把他的老二剁掉
In exchange for me not chopping off his dick,
他慷慨地给我了一份资料的复印件
he graciously supplied me with a copy of the files.
里面有那天在基地工作的所有人员名单
There was a list of everyone working on the base that day.
然后你们拿它对比了伤亡名单
So you compared it to the list of casualties?
有一个人没找到
One name was unaccounted for.
一个叫利奥·菲茨帕克里特的私人保镖
Private contractor named Leo Fitzpatrick.
你应该知道怎么找到这个利奥吧
I'm guessing you know how to find this Leo?
当然了  兵哥
Of course, soldier boy.
凯·普罗科特市长
我从没有一个人过
I've never been on my own before.
以后不会了
You're not anymore.
先生
Sir.
妮娜·克鲁兹
Nina Cruz.
让她进来
Send her in.
-市长先生  -怎么了  副警长
- Mr. Mayor. - What is it, Deputy?
上次你的地检官放走的那三个人
The last three guys your district attorney cut loose
之后都遭了黑手
were all royally fucked up after the fact.
自卫队员吗
Vigilante?
我认为不仅如此
I think it's more than that.
你看  三起释放都与你有关
See, all three releases were connected to you.
无论这些自卫队员是谁
Whoever the vigilante is,
他们知道你控制了地方检察官
they know you've got the DA in your pocket.
有人在向你示威
Someone's sending you a message.
洛特斯警长
Sheriff Lotus.
你怎么想  副警长
What do you think, Deputy?
布罗克一向嘴上抱怨
I think Brock makes a lot of noise,
但他绝不会那样对付你
but he'd never come after you like that.
那给我查出是谁
Then get me a name.
可能会惹上麻烦
It could get messy.
那就把麻烦处理掉
Then you'll clean it up.
你雇我做你的耳目
You hired me to be your eyes and your ears.
我不介意处理麻烦
I don't mind doing the cleaning,
但价钱得提高
but that costs more.
那你最好物有所值
Then you better be worth it.
-警长  -海伦  这破网又断了
- Sheriff? - Helen, the damn Internet is broken again.
我一会儿看看  鲍曼夫妇想见你
I'll take a look. The Bowmans are here to see you.
该死
Oh, shit.
我要带他们上楼吗
Shall I bring them upstairs?
不用  不用  我去吧
No. No, I'll do it.
你来修修这个
Try to fix this.
-鲍曼先生和夫人  -警长
- Mr. and Mrs. Bowman. - Sheriff.
想去我办公室谈谈吗
Would you like to come up to my office and talk?
法医不肯把丽贝卡的尸体给我们
The county coroner won't release Rebecca's body to us.
是  确实
Yes, that's true.
很不幸  暂时不能带走尸体
Unfortunately, the body can't be released
要等法医查清真正死因
until the coroner has determined an official cause of death.
葬礼必须马上举行
The funeral must be held immediately.
-我理解  -这是我们的习俗
- I understand. - This is our way.
我们
It's--
我们的女儿已经去世一周了
it's been a week since our daughter's passing.
我明白  我保证整个警局
I know, and I assure you my entire department
都在夜以继日的调查您女儿的案子
is working day and night on your daughter's case.
你没有权利不把她还给我们
You have no right to keep her from us.
-鲍曼夫人  -求求你  让我们使她安息吧
- Mrs. Bowman-- - Please, let us put her to rest.
好吧  我去打几个电话
All right, let me make some calls.
我尽量让他们加快速度  好吗
I'll try to move things along, okay?
我保证
I promise.
来  我们走吧
Come. Let's go.
再次  节哀顺变
Again, I'm sorry for your loss.
虽然科技突破了文化间的障碍
With technology crossing cultural boundaries,
但网络道德问题仍几乎无解
computer ethics are virtually intractable.
为什么  我们如何在文化相对性的背景下
Why? Well, how can we set a global standard
设定一个全球性的标准
when cultural relativism makes it impossible?
这里的我们  我是指他们
And by we, I mean they.
这里的他们  我是指美国政府
And by they, I mean the United States government.
但他们可以执行第18章第1030条
But what they can do is enforce title 18, section 1030.
如果你被发现入侵一台电脑
If you are caught accessing a computer
试图窃取信息或损坏网络
with intent to steal information or damage a network,
你将被抓进监狱
you will go to jail.
当你出来时
And when you're out,
你会获得六位数年薪的安全分析师的工作
you'll get a six-figure gig as a security analyst.
下课  回家吧
That's it. Go home.
大家下周见
I'll see you all next week.
很好
That's great.
去下一站
Go to the next station.
请远离车门
Please stand clear of the doors.
-我上车了  -收到  我在路上
- I'm on the train. - Copy. I'm on the move.
下一站  华莱士街
Next stop, Wallace Street.
搞什么  伙计
What the fuck, bro?
混蛋  让开
Asshole. Move!
-他在车上  -收到
- He's on the train. - Copy.
让开
Move!
刚刚好  兵哥
About time, soldier boy.
带他上车
Just get him in the car!
快上车
Get the fuck in the car.
快点  快他妈上车啊
Come on, get the fuck in the car.
-好  搞定了  -我操  快点啊
- Yeah, got him. - Jesus fucking Christ, come on.
十七个月前
柯特
Hi, Kurt.
玛吉
Maggie.
我听说你回来了
I--I heard you were back.
你来这干什么
What are you doing here?
我给你买了点东西
I brought you some groceries.
为什么
Why?
感觉没什么人帮你忙
I don't see anyone else lining up to help you out.
我不需要帮忙
I don't need any help.
是  你当然不需要
Yeah, of course you don't.
我能进去吗
Are you gonna let me in?
可以
Yeah.
进来吧
我还
I haven't, uh...
没时间看这些信
had time to go through my mail yet.
我每周都会给医院打电话问你的情况
I called the hospital every week to check on you.
没人跟我说过
No one told me.
我让他们别说
I asked them not to.
我知道那件事
I know that it was Calvin
都是因为加尔文和他的人
and his goons that did that to you.
为什么你不举报他们
Why didn't you report them?
说是你问的  还是加尔文
That you asking or Calvin?
别傻了
Don't be an asshole.
他要是知道我来过这儿会杀了我的
You know he'd kill me if he knew I was here.
他这么对你我真想杀了他
I want to kill him for what he did to you.
只是
It's...
太惊人了  两兄弟虽然长得如此相像
it's just amazing how two brothers can be so different
但又完全不同
and so alike at the same time.
我得回去了
I have to get home.
这是我的号码
My cell.
有事打给我
If you need anything.
-我操  完了  -怎么了
- Oh, shit. Shit. Shit. - What?
来电  加尔文
加尔文
Calvin.
你他妈到底在哪
Where the fuck are you?
不  我不能这样  柯特
I can't-- I can't do this, Kurt.
我明白
I know.
我们不会一直这样的
It's not always gonna be like this.
你还觉得你救得了他吗
You think you can still get him out?
不觉得  但我做过
No, I don't. I did.
但那件事后
But after this...
我知道他回不了头了
I know there's no coming back for him.
我要想想怎么才能让他进监狱
I just need to figure out how to put him away.
就是需要花点时间
That's gonna take some time.
时间不会改变任何事的  柯特
Time's not gonna change anything, Kurt.
那你要我怎么做
What do you want me to do?
现在就杀了他
Just kill him now.
我不能杀了自己兄弟
I can't kill my own brother.
他是汉克的爸爸
He's Hank's father.
柯特  小的时候
Kurt, when I was a little girl,
我父亲总是吓我
my father poisoned me with fear.
他让我坚信只有待在像他一样的男人身边
He made sure that I would only ever feel safe
才会有安全感
if I was with a man just like him.
而我后来也欣然接受了
And I just accepted that.
事情本应是这样的
That that's how things would always be.
但接着你回来了
And then you came back.
人生中我第一次觉得
For the first time in my life,
事情或许会有不同
I thought things could be different.
但这不仅关乎我
But this isn't about me.
我害怕我儿子
I'm terrified that my son
以后也会变成加尔文那样
is gonna turn out to be just like Calvin
像我父亲那样
and just like my father,
刻薄  可恶  暴力
mean, hateful, violent.
我不会让这一切发生的
I won't let that happen.
你要相信我  玛吉
You have to trust me, Maggie.
这个混蛋居然还活着
I assume there's a good reason
一定是有什么原因了
why this son of a bitch is still breathing.
你好啊  利奥
Hey, Leo.
我靠
Jesus. Fuck!
贾伯在哪
Where's Job?
什么
What?
贾伯在哪
Where's Job?
贾伯他妈的在哪
Where the fuck is Job?
我不知道那是谁
I don't know who that is.
继续给我编
Tell me another lie. Please.
看出来这是怎么回事了吗
See how this works?
你每跟我们胡扯一次  她就揍你
Every time you bullshit us, she's gonna hit you.
等她累了  就换我来
When she gets tired, I'm gonna start.
她下手狠
She hits hard.
我下手更狠
I hit harder.
懂了吗
You understand?
你抓走了我们的朋友
You took our friend.
我们要他回来
We want him back.
给我松绑  我就考虑下要不要帮你
Untie me, I'll think about helping you.
住手
Stop.
这货要是晕了就没法说话了
The boy can't talk if he ain't conscious.
把"尼基塔"带到厨房去
Take Nikita to the kitchen.
让我和糖果试试
Give me and Sugar a minute.
去吧
Go.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
你只不过做了我们都想做的事
You were just doing what we all wanted to.
所有人突然都不见了
Just everybody disappeared all at once.
你明白吗
You know?
都是我的错
It's all my fault.
贾伯知道其中风险
Job knew the risks.
我们都知道
We all did.
我说的不是贾伯
I'm not talking about Job.
我在山上待了将近两年
You know, I spent nearly two years up in those hills
为以前的事责怪我自己
blaming myself for everything that happened.
如果这一切都是你造成的
Now, that would have been a big waste of time
那我真是太浪费时间了
if this was all your fault.
这一切真是一塌糊涂
Everything got so fucked up.
是啊
Yeah, it did.
菲茨帕克里特先生改主意了
Mr. Fitzpatrick has had a change of heart.
是吗
Really?
你出门总带着手锯吗
You always travel with a handsaw?
这是必备工具  兵哥哥
Tools of the trade. Soldier boy.
你最好原封不动把刚才的话告诉他们
It would be best for you if you told them what you told us.
热那亚之后  贾伯连着被审了三个月
After Genoa, Job was interrogated for three months straight.
逼他供出名字  日期  一切情报
They worked him for names, dates, everything.
但他屁都没说
But he wouldn't give them shit.
真是个倔强的混蛋
That stubborn motherfucker.
所以他们就放弃了  把他列为长押人员
So they gave up and they marked him for EDE.
那是什么
What the hell is that?
长期关押利用
Extended detainment and exploitation.
通常关押那些施加额外激励
It's usually reserved for enemies of the state
便可加以利用的国家公敌
who require some extra motivation.
他现在在哪
So where is he now?
妈的他到底在哪
Where the fuck is he?!
他们把他关在秘密监狱
They're keeping him in a black site.
美军臭名昭著的虐囚监狱
是超严密的黑牢  阿布格莱布监狱和它一比
A supermax hellhole that makes Abu Ghraib
就像四季酒店似的
look like the Four Seasons.
-我们怎么才能进去  -你们进不去
- How do we get in there? - You don't.
-怎么进  -根本没人进得去
- How? - No one gets in, period.
哥们儿  回答错误
Wrong answer, homes.
别  等等
Wait! Wait!
没人能进去  但如果你们有钱
No one gets in, but we might be able to buy him out
也许能把他赎出来
if you have the cash.
-把他的脚剁了  -不  别
- Cut his fucking foot off. - No, don't!
钱不是给我的
The money is not for me.
政府需要合理的推诿
Look, the government needs plausible deniability,
所以这些地方有完全的自主权
so these places, they are completely autonomous.
管事儿的人不听命于任何人
The guys who are running them, they answer to no one.
有时候他们会做交易
Sometimes they'll deal.
多少钱
How much?
你有多少
How much do you have?
看来提前退休是没戏了
So much for early retirement.
贾伯知道我们把钱用光会气死的
Job is gonna be really pissed that we spent it all.
他会消气的
He'll get over it.
打过去
Make the call.
真高兴这么多个月来你都没动这钱
Glad you kept it safe for us all these months.
我留着是以备不时之需
Yeah, I was saving it for a rainy day.
我达成了交易
I made the deal.
你在说什么  你确定吗
What are you talking about? Are you sure?
钱在这儿  我正盯着呢
The money is here. I am staring right at it.
但如果他死了  你一分钱也得不到  懂吗
But if he dies, you get nothing, you hear me?
他妈的什么情况
What the fuck just happened?
他们已经计划好让贾伯消失了
Job is scheduled to go dark.
什么意思
What the hell does that mean?
意思是他对他们没用处了
It means they have no further use for him.
-什么时候  -不清楚
- When? - Unclear.
可能是两天  也可能是两小时
It could be two days, it could be two hours.
你想他活着回来  我们现在就得出发
You want him back alive, we need to go now.
我就假装我没看到
Okay, I'm gonna pretend I didn't see that.
如果食物掉到地上  五秒内捡起来就可以吃
没听说过五秒规则吗
You never heard of the five-second rule?
你解剖完丽贝卡·鲍曼了吗
You finished with Rebecca Bowman?
已经切开并缝好了  但要完全搞定验尸报告
Well, she's Y'd and tied, but it's gonna be some time
还需要一段时间
before I finish the full pathology.
不行  我们没时间了  丹
No, we are out of time, Dan.
我需要把她的尸体送回她家
I need to get this girl's body home to her family.
希望你不是要我给一个
I hope you're not asking me to rush the autopsy
可疑连环杀手的受害者仓促验尸
for the victim of an alleged serial killer.
那就说下你到目前为止的发现
Tell me what you have so far, then, all right?
那就是目前我还在验尸中
What I've got is an autopsy in progress.
别挑战我极限  丹  别他妈现在挑战我极限
Don't test me, Dan. Don't fucking test me right now.
老天啊  布罗克  淡定
Jesus Christ, Brock, relax.
这个
Well...
刺伤的伤口和软组织撕裂
puncture wounds and tearing of the soft tissue
和动物咬痕一致
are consistent with animal bites,
但极有可能是死后造成的
but they were most likely caused postmortem.
他把她扔在树林里时她已经死了
Right, she was already dead when he dumped her body in the woods.
-我们早知道这个了  对吧  -是的
- We knew that, right? - Yes.
但他切开她胸部挖出她心脏的时候
But she was still alive when he filleted her chest
她还是活着的
and cut her heart out.
简直和《夺宝奇兵2》里如出一辙
That's some real "Temple of Doom" shit.
也就是说和另外两个女生情况一样
So it is the same as the other two girls.
变态狗杂种
Sick son of a bitch.
我赌一周的薪水在她体内能找到
I'll bet a week's pay the tox screen will find
类似的安定和杜冷丁成分
similar traces of Valium and Demerol in her system.
他使用的剂量可能刚好让她保持清醒
He probably used just enough to keep her conscious,
但又让她无力反抗
but knock the fight out of her.
该死  丹  给我点有用的
God damn it, Dan. Just give me something.
任何能抓住这个混蛋的东西
Anything to catch this asshole.
一个指纹  DNA  随便什么
A fingerprint, DNA, something.
这人很厉害  布罗克
This guy's good, Brock.
他掩盖痕迹的手法很专业
He covers his tracks like a pro.
操你妈  也就是说你什么都没发现
Fuck you! You've got nothing, then.
实际上
Actually...
我有所发现
I've got the opposite of nothing.
我操
Holy shit.
我从没在这里见过你  对吗
I haven't seen you in here before, have I?
你看着不像这里的顾客
You don't look like our usual clientele.
我要一杯咖啡就好
I'll just have a cup of coffee.
想要点些什么吗
Could I help you with something?
一块馅饼多少钱
How much for a piece of pie?
3块
$3.
我只有这么多了
That's all I got.
来杯咖啡怎么样
How about a cup of coffee?
馅饼记我账下
I'll pay for the pie.
再请一杯牛奶行吗
And a glass of milk?
没问题  你想要什么都行
Sure. Whatever you like.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
雪莉
Cherry.
你的真名是什么
What's your real name?
珍妮弗
Jennifer.
进来吧
Come on in.
随处看看
Look around.
你的父母在哪里  珍妮弗
Where are your parents, Jennifer?
不知道  也不关心
Don't know. Don't care.
你有自己的浴室  热浴盆
You have your own bathroom, Jacuzzi tub.
一大推干净浴巾
There's plenty of fresh towels.
衣橱里有衣服
Clothing in the closet.
应该合你的身
Should all fit you nicely.
请自便
So help yourself.
你想要上我吗
Are you gonna fuck me?
我只想让你觉得舒服点
I just want you to feel comfortable,
仅此而已
nothing more.
你一定累了  休息吧
You must be tired. I'll let you get some rest.
你想要待多久都行
You can stay as long as you like.
这是谁的房间
Hey, whose room is this?
一位对我很重要的人
Someone who was very special to me.
恐怕我们要在这里分开了
I'm afraid our time together has come to an end.
站起来走吧
Start walking.
走
Go.
接着走
Keep moving.
慢点
Easy. Easy. Easy.
有我呢
I got you. I got you.
I got you.
有我呢
你们他妈的总算来了
It's about motherfucking time.
我们带你回家
Let's get you home.
这他妈的是哪一出
What the fuck is this?
其实不用问你就应该知道了
If you have to ask, you already know.
以后要记着  我们不做交易
For future reference, we don't make deals.
我只是想知道
I was just wondering.
我像那种不知道这一套的傻逼吗
Do I look like the kind of motherfucker who wouldn't know that?
起来
Get the fuck up.
妈的
Fuck.
你想怎么处置他
What do you want to do with him?
是啊  贾伯
Yeah, Job.
你现在要怎么做
What are you gonna do now--
我们可以走了吗
Can we go now?
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?
他妈的离我远点
Stay the fuck away from me.
你这个不知感激的婊子
You ungrateful bitch.
对不起  请不要伤害我
I'm sorry. Please don't hurt me.
不
No.
我给了你自由
I gave you freedom!
我给了你住的地方
I gave you a place to stay!
我给了你一切
I gave you everything.
但还是不够  是吗
But it was never enough, was it?
哥们  你有的是时间啊
Man, you got all the time in the world.
有两位要出门
We got two on the gate.
C区犯人  准备放风
C-block inmates, prepare for yard detail.
所有C区犯人十五分钟后放风
Yard detail in 15 minutes for all C-block inmates.
大麻已被X光检测过了
Smokes are being X-rayed.
等你出狱就能看到
They'll be waiting for you on the other side.
谢谢  但我真正需要的是
Thanks, but what I really need
你正视身边的问题
is for you to pull your head out of your ass.
我不懂
I don't understand.
在女妖镇拍色情电影你是怎么想的
What the hell were you thinking shooting porn in Banshee?
你和普罗科特谈过了
You talked to Proctor.
他对你们这些傻逼厌烦了
He's getting tired of your fuckups.
我也是
And so am I.
我发现了一个赚钱的机会
I saw an opportunity to earn--
小子  你要分清轻重缓急
You need to get your priorities straight, boy.
搜刮小钱
Scrounging for chump change,
那是黑鬼跟墨西哥佬干的事
that's for niggers and spics.
我们为什么还要听那个混蛋的呢
Why the fuck are we still answering to this asshole anyway?
我们的势力比他大的多
We have an army 10 times bigger than his.
因为我这么说了
Because I say so.
还有其它我不想说的原因
There are some other reasons I don't want to get into,
但你只需要知道这一条就好了
but for your purposes, that's the only one you need.
你听懂了吗
Do you hear me?
明白了
I hear you.
别再搞砸了
No more fuck-ups.
不会了  先生
No, sir.
很好
Good.
赶紧滚  别耽误我吃午饭
Now get the fuck out of here before I miss lunch.
周二吃玉米卷
It's taco Tuesday.
凯
Kai.
抱歉  米里亚姆
I'm sorry, Miriam.
法律上我没法让他们把尸体还回来
I can't legally do anything to make them release the body.
法律上
Legally?
法律什么时候能阻止你了
Since when has legal ever stopped you?
一旦可以  我就会亲自
I'll personally bring Rebecca home to you
把丽贝卡送回你身边  我保证
as soon as I possibly can, I promise.
当丽贝卡离开我们时
When Rebecca left us,
我祈祷她能回来
I prayed that she'd return.
但你收留她以后
But when you took her in,
我就知道上帝将我的祈祷置若罔闻
I knew that God had forsaken my prayers.
她的死都是你的错  凯
Her blood is on your hands, Kai.
因此  我永远都不会原谅你
And for that, I will never forgive you.
你把从我从地狱里救出来
You rescued me from that hellhole
第一件事就是带我来这儿吗
and the first place you bring me back is here?
宝贝  你真无情
Baby, you heartless.
我们都再喝一杯吧
I think we could all use another drink.
这是珍藏十八年的格伦利物威士忌
This is an 18-year-old bottle of Glenlivet.
我是留着特殊场合喝的
I've been saving it for a special occasion.
来吧  贾伯
Come on, Job.
一口闷
Drink up.
我只是需要休息一下
I just need to get some rest.
然后拿我热那亚的分成
Then I'm going to grab my take from Genoa,
之后回城里
head back into the city,
也许会给自己买个顶层公寓
maybe set myself up with a penthouse.
怎么了
What?
谁来赶紧说句话
Somebody better start talking now.
收买他们可不便宜
Buying them off wasn't cheap.
利奥带着钱走了
Leo got away with the bag.
有多少
How much?
全部
All of it.
所以到头来  我一无所有
So after all that time, I got nothing.
后面的房间还是你的  贾伯
You still got your place in the back, Job.
不  他不能再住在那了
No, he's not gonna stay in a back room.
你来跟我一起住
You're gonna come stay with me.
我会照顾你的
I'm gonna take care of you.
孩子们都不在  很安静的
The kids are away. It'll be quiet.
戈登怎么办
And what about Gordon?
我忘记了  他还在不在
I lost track. Is he in or is he out?
戈登没有挺过来
Gordon didn't make it.
谢谢你们去救我
Thank you all for coming to get me.
下次可以告诉我  为什么要等20个月才来
Next time you can tell me why it took 20 months.
这他妈怎么回事
What the hell is this?
卢卡斯·胡德
Lucas Hood.
你因谋杀丽贝卡·鲍曼被捕了
You're under arrest for the murder of Rebecca Bowman.
布罗克  这是开玩笑吗
Brock, is this a joke?
先生  抱歉
Sir, I'm sorry,
但我们有逮捕令
but we have a warrant.
布罗克  你知道不是我干的
Brock, you know I didn't do it.
是吗  那你跟我解释解释
Yeah? Then maybe you want to tell me
为什么她的车里会有你的血
how your blood ended up inside of her car.
没话吗
Nothing?
看来你也不知道是怎么把她肚子搞大的吧
And I'm guessing you have no idea how you knocked her up either.
什么
What?
没听错  邦克  把他拷上
Yeah, Bunker, put the cuffs on this man.
我们走
Let's go.
先生
Sir.
好的  等等  这...
Okay, wait a minute. This is--
克鲁兹  退后
Hey. Cruz, stand down.
我让你他妈的退后
I said stand the fuck down.
我们走  把他关车里去
Let's go. Get him in the car.
没关系
It's okay.
抱歉
Sorry.
我不在的时候  是不是错过了什么
So, did I miss anything while I was gone?